Gosh, it's hot!
Yeah, summer's in full swing.
By the way, Desumi-san.
There's a lot to do in the summer, isn't there?
Is there anything you'd
like to do as a couple?
What a great idea, Fudo!
Let's see... what would be best?
Barbecues, fireworks displays...
Let's see...
A trip to the mountains would be nice,
but I think it has to be the beach!
The beach?!
Fudo?
Swimsuits?!
Hey! Fudo?
Opening Theme
"Koi wa Explosion (feat. Culverin Bear [Hiroki Yasumoto])"
Vocals: Masayoshi Oishi
Lyrics • Music • Mixing: Masayoshi Oishi
Episode 6    As Long as We're at the Beach...
Tense
Aha!
Truly becoming of my rival, Reaper Princess!
Tense
She exudes a forbidding aura,
even during lunchtime!
Tense
What could be the poor recipient
of the fire in her gaze?
Green Tea Pudding
Tiramisu
Pasta Set
Dessert Options
Hmmm...
Green Tea Pudding
Tiramisu
You let me down, big-time!
Don't you know you've got
an image to maintain?
You were the one person around here
with a ferocity I could respect.
Now look at you, eating pasta with
that goofy look on your face!
Why'd you want to join
Gekko in the first place?
I didn't. My family applied for me.
What are you, an idol?!
But that entrance exam ain't easy.
How the hell'd you pass, then?
I just did my best,
and they put me in a leadership role.
She never meant to apply? Is that
why she doesn't take it seriously?
Hey, Beast!
Don't you think a beach would be
a great place for our next attack?
Huh?!
All squad leaders and Princess Series members,
report to the conference room at once.
I repeat.
They don't usually call
us in at this time of day.
All squad leaders and Princess Series members,
report to the conference room at once.
Hey!
Drop the pasta and get moving!
Beast Princess and Reaper Princess,
now in attendance!
Allow me to explain!
Secret Society Gekko is an
uncompromising hierarchy!
Supreme Leader Bosslar
Monsters (Leaders)
Bear Monster
Snake Monster
Wolf Monster
Eagle Monster
Lion Monster
Rabbit Monster
Princess Series (Sub-Leaders)
Reaper
Steel
Blood
Heat
Beast
Judgment
Moonlight Soldiers
Its six squadrons are led by
their six strongest monsters,
with the Princess Series serving
below them as sub-leaders!
Allow me to reveal the reason
I have called you all here today.
I have decided to create a new monster
and establish a new squadron!
Reaper Princess, step forward!
Congratulations!
Reaper Princess, Desumi Magahara!
I am promoting you
from Princess Series to monster!
You'll undergo enhancement surgery,
be fused with an animal,
and acquire greater power than ever before!
You... You want to make me a monster?
Damn it! They passed me over for her?!
H-Hang on a min—
You're moving up in the world at last!
I always knew you had it in you!
Welcome to the monster world!
These bodies are awesome, girl!
It's frustrating, but I'm gonna catch up soon!
Just wait and see!
Congratulations, Reaper-chan!
You'll be just like us!
Drone Rabbit-senpai?
She's so pretty...
If I could become a cute monster
like her, maybe it wouldn't be so bad.
Reaper Princess!
Fusion Concept Diagram
I intend to fuse you with a mountain gorilla!
A fusion between the two ultimate primates!
A true miracle of chemistry!
Wait a minute!
The enhancement surgery
will take place tomorrow!
W-Wait...
That is all!
Dismissed!
If I become a monster,
it'll mean big changes to life as I know it.
No beach date, either, probably.
But I can't exactly say no...
Lifetime Soldier
Hey, Desumi!
How ya doin'?
Dad...
Got a message from Bosslar-sama.
He's promotin' you, he said!
That's my perfect little girl!
One, two...
Congratulations, Sis!
Never thought we'd have a monster in our
very own family... It's a dream come true!
Now, dear, don't cry...
I was a combatant all through to retirement,
so it's makin' me so happy...
Give it your best, Desumi!
Mom...
The truth is... I'm not sure I want...
And after seeing' how hard you been workin',
your sister's finally started
comin' out of her shell.
Go on, dear.
Talk to your big sister.
Big Sis.
Urami...
I'm gonna join Gekko when I graduate.
You better keep fightin',
even after you're a monster.
You're my idol, Big Sis.
I hear ya, Urami.
No worries.
See ya, Desumi!
Take care of yourself!
See ya! Keep fightin', Big Sis!
My Gekko teammates and my family
are all so happy for me...
They'll all be really upset if I
turn the promotion down, right?
I wonder what Fudo would say.
H-Hey!
Fudo
F-Fudo?!
Wh-Whaddya want?!
That adorable Hakata dialect!
I was just thinking about you,
and I realized I wanted to hear your voice.
Is something up?
Your greeting was a little
bit different than usual.
Nah, I'm sure I heard wrong.
Don't worry about it.
Give me one hour!
I'm here, Desumi-san
Fudo?
I see.
They want to make you a monster.
Yeah, and combine me with a gorilla.
You'd be the world's cutest gorilla!
This is serious for me, okay?!
Hey, Fudo.
What do you think I should do?
It doesn't matter what I think.
What do you want to do?
What I want to do...
Now that I think about it, this whole time,
I never even thought about it.
Gekko Interview Site
Desumi-san...
Your kindness toward everyone around you
is one of the things I love best about you.
But you should turn a little bit of that
kindness toward yourself every now and then.
Now, what do you want to do?
That's right.
It is okay for me to choose, isn't it?
If I become a gorilla,
it's going to be harder to do my manicures,
my cooking, my handicrafts...
It would make it harder
to see you, too, Fudo.
I want to go back to the
amusement park with you.
I want to have our afterschool date.
And I wouldn't feel comfortable going
to the beach in any body but this one.
I don't want to give up on any of that.
Fudo...
Meeting you has made me want
to do so many new things.
If I was still the person I was before you,
I probably would have gone along with
what everyone else wanted for me.
But...
I'm sorry, everyone.
I can't become a gorilla yet!
I want to be able to keep
leaning on Fudo like this.
Wh-What?!
What do you mean, you don't
want to become a monster?!
That's my decision.
I have no regrets.
Are you freakin' nuts, Reaper?!
This is your chance to acquire true power!
You reject your great leader's generous offer?!
Yes.
Magnificent!
You are truly a wonder, Reaper Princess!
Huh?
Your style is to fight only with
your naturally-given gifts!
Truly, you have the heart of a martial artist!
You believe accepting the power of an animal
would be admitting your own weakness!
Burned
All right! A round of applause
for Reaper Princess!
You all could learn a thing or two from her!
I told them I didn't want to become a monster!!
Fudo
Thanks, Fudo
You followed your heart
and turned them down!
You're amazing, Desumi-san!
Hey, it's Reaper Princess!
She must have gotten her enhancement surgery!
So that's what she looks like after
being combined with the gorilla?
Yeah! She's more intimidating than ever!
Love After World Domination!
Wow, the weather is great!
I'm all ready! Let's go!
One moment, Reaper Princess.
Ack
What are you doing with that beach stuff?
Just because we're at the beach
doesn't mean it's a vacation.
Honestly.
Now, are you sure about
that tip you received?
Yes, sir!
Absolutely certain!
You mean it, Fudo?
Yeah.
This Saturday, we'll be doing a test drive
of King Gelato Robo at Shonan Beach.
Allow me to explain!
King Gelato Robo is a 12-piece combining
robot designed to fight giant monsters!
The beach...
Does that mean...
Yes!
It's our chance for a beach date at last!
That's great, Fudo!
Sparkle
I can't wait for Saturday!
Hello? Is this Bear-sama?
I've just gotten a secret
tip about the heroes' activities.
Gekko Aquatic Combat Loadout
Reaper Princess
(Swimsuit Provided)
But it appears the heroes
have not yet arrived.
Then you should make careful
preparations for their arrival.
Our mission is to investigate
and demolish the heroes' robot.
Gekko Aquatic Combat Loadout
Culverin Bear & Steel Princess
(Swimsuits Provided)
It's important to act
carefully and discreetly.
This is a combined mission
between our three squadrons.
Let's all work together,
Reaper-san, Beast-sa—
Oh? Why are you hiding behind those rocks?
I a-ain't hidin'!
I just...
Well...
Majima
Don't my outfit seem a little
different from what you guys got?
Gekko Aquatic Combat Loadout
Beast Princess
(Swimsuit Provided)
Certainly not.
It looks wonderful on you.
Yes!
Y-You think?
Hey, Steel.
Don't stand next to me.
Buzz off!
But why? We should work together!
Just get lost, damn it!
Retreat! Retreat!
Oh, sorry!
I accidentally fired the missiles!
They didn't hit anybody.
I don't... think.
Probably.
They anticipated our sabotage mission.
A submarine...
Is that a part of their giant robot?
It's so much nicer out here than in there!
Misaki-san, no beer!
Oh, chill out.
As long as we're at the beach...
No way!
We're not here to have fun!
Now, now.
None of that, Misaki-kun.
That one's still warm.
Ta-dah
You'll want to drink these.
Professor...
Now, now, Haru-kun.
I know we're doing a test drive,
but it's just for Gelato Submarine.
And this one just forms the robot's calf,
so it's not exactly essential.
Then why did you make it?!
Red's coming here!
What's the plan, Reaper?
You think we can handle
the mission on our own?
H-Hey!
Found you, Fudo!
Oh, Desumi-sa—
Wh-What's wrong, Fudo?
Hey!
I was so taken aback by your
loveliness that I forgot to breathe!
Cut it out! You scared me!
Don't stare at me like that!
I didn't choose the outfit myself,
but it's a little embarrassing...
Oh so precious
Oh so precious!
Now, let's have the beach date of our dreams!
That reminds me...
There was something I wanted to try.
Okay! Let's do it!
She intends to execute the
plan completely on her own.
Reaper Princess is truly impressive.
Meanwhile, I always get
stuck evaluating risk...
That's the difference between us.
But... that ends today!
I, Beast Princess, A.K.A. Kiki Majima,
will finally gain some respect—
She's torturing him!
She's torturing him!!!
Well?
Can't move now, can you?
I can't!
Reaper Princess... She truly is merciless!
And there's one other thing
I really wanted to do!
Sh-She's not finished yet?!
All ready?
Menace
She's gonna smash his head open!
She's gonna smash his head open!!
She smashed it!!
She smashed it!
Hey, cutie!
Hang on!
Truly, is this not destiny?
H-Hang on.
I know you...
You're Blue Gelato!
Wow! You know me?
That's fantastic!
Come enjoy your summer with a celebrity!
You're every bit the pig I'd heard...
Hands off!
Where's Reaper?
She's deeply infiltrated their ranks!
Hey.
Just admit you want a piece of this.
Come back, my sweet honey!
I gotta say...
Desumi-chan, you said you were
Fudo's friend or something...
But it looks to me like you're dating.
grin
A-Are not!
shake
So dang cute!
I made chilled noodles.
That's our boy!
Let's eat!
Join us.
Oh, thanks.
Wow!
Fireworks!
Surprise!
They're so pretty!
Well done, Professor!
So much smoke!
So you're the one I have to thank?
Thank?
Fudo's become a better man than before.
And he's sharing more sides of himself.
I think that's because of you, Desumi-chan.
Are you watching, Desumi-san?
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, it is, Fudo!
Handheld
200 Sparklers
Look what we bought!
Let's all do them together!
Okay!
Sounds great!
Fudo...
You really are an amazing man...
Since I first started going out with you,
it's been nothing but
wonderful things every day!
I hope the young people
are enjoying themselves.
Now, time to fire the final show-stopper.
clunk
Finally lost him...
Talk about persistent!
Hey, Beast!
Reaper?
After all she did to Red,
it's like nothing happened.
But of course,
not even she could destroy the whole robot—
She freaking did it!
That last firework was a really big one!
She really knows no bounds!
What a wonderful day it's been!
She's...
It looks delicious!
Liar!
Episode 7    Desumi Magahara Is the Monster I Made
Episode 7 is gonna be
"Desumi Magahara Is the Monster I Made."
So watch it, okay?